Works Progress Administration (WPA) Phonodisc Collection
Works Progress Administration (WPA) Phonodisc Collection
- 1936 season
  - Program No. 68 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Folk Lore Choir, 1936; wpa_phono_068; folk songs, performed by chorus and various soloists with piano accompaniment.; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Swedish folk songs: Flickorna de små uti dansen da gå; Ach hor du lilla flicka; Early American song: Prairie flower; La pastorella; Italian mountain song: Serenata delle Alpi; WPA spot; Neapolitan serenade: O mari canta; Stornellata Romanesca.
  - Program No. 69 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1936; wpa_phono_069; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    The Picador; WPA spot; The Blue Danube; Finale to Dance of the Hours from La Gioconda
  - Program No. 70 Works Progress Administration Presents Brooklyn Symphony Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_070; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Ballet from the Petite Suite; Meditation from Thais, Carmella Ipolitov [?], violin; WPA spot; Russian Folk songs: I danced with a mosquito; Cradle song; Song dance
  - Program No. 71 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Negro Choir, 1936; wpa_phono_071; spirituals and folks songs, by chorus and various soloists with and without piano accompaniment; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Every Time I Feel the Spirit; Got a Home at Last, sung by soloist D. A. Scott; Now is the Needy Time; WPA spot; Wade in the Water, sung by soloist J. B. Jones; Swing Low, Sweet Chariot; Heaven, Sung by soloist Gonzalo James; Steal away, sung by soloist Mamie Titus.
  - Program No. 72 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1936; wpa_phono_072; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    March Militaire no. 2; Minuet; WPA spot; Selections from Scenes Pittoresques: March; Air de Ballet
  - Program No. 73 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_073; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Mignon; WPA spot; Musette, from King Christian II suite; Polonaise
  - Program No. 74 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1936; wpa_phono_074; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00 (Oversize 1)
    High School Cadets March; Mazurka from La Czarina; WPA spot; Orpheus in Hades, aka Orpheus in the Underworld, arranged for concert band.
  - Program No. 75 Works Progress Administration Presents New York Civic Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_075; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Ocean! Thou Mighty Monster, from Oberon; WPA spot; Waltz of the Flowers, from the Nutcracker suite
  - Program No. 76 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_076; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Monkey's wedding variation from American Fantasy; Before the Dawn from Deserted Gardens for piano and orchestra; WPA spot; To a Comedian from Hollywood Suite; Indian War Dance.
  - Program No. 77 Works Progress Administration Presents the Madrigal Singers, 1936; wpa_phono_077; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Happy oh happy he; Now is the month of May; Adagio from Trio in D minor; WPA spot; Clorinda, false, adieu; Willy, prithee, go to bed
  - Program No. 78 Works Progress Administration Presents New York Civic Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_078; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Symphony no. 5 in E minor. Second movement, Andante Cantabile; WPA spot
  - Program No. 79 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1936; wpa_phono_079; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    The Call of the Wild; Rustle of Spring; WPA spot; Invitation to the waltz [Dance]
  - Program No. 80 Works Progress Administration Presents Brooklyn Symphony Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_080; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to The Marriage of Figaro; WPA spot; En bateau, from Petite suite; Ride of the Valkyries, from Die Walküre
  - Program No. 81 Works Progress Administration Presents New York Civic Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_081; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    In Bohemia, Op. 28; WPA spot; Popular Russian Dances suite: In the Garden; Kamarinskaya; unpublished score for orchestra: second movement, fifth movement
  - Program No. 82 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_082; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to open Shakh-Senem; WPA spot; excerpts from Elegy, from King Christian II; excerpts from March Tsar Sultan from the Fairy Tale suite
  - Program No. 83 Works Progress Administration Presents the Madrigal Singers, 1936; wpa_phono_083; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Second Movement from Trio in C major; WPA spot; Come Again Sweet Love, a capella chorus; April is in my Mistress' Face, a capella chorus; Mother, I Will Have a Husband; Second Movement from G Minor Trio.
  - Program No. 84 Works Progress Administration Presents New York Civic Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_084; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    excerpts from The Judge, from the Oratorio Death and Life [unplayable]; WPA spot; The Flight of the Bumblebee; Czardas
  - Program No. 85 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Knickerbocker Little Symphony, 1936; wpa_phono_085; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Kaiser waltz; WPA spot; March hymn; Moment musicale
  - Program No. 86 Works Progress Administration Presents Brooklyn Symphony Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_086; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Oberon; WPA spot; Cortège from Petite suite
  - Program No. 87 Works Progress Administration Presents New York Civic Orchestra, 1936; wpa_phono_087; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Scherzo from A midsummer night's dream; WPA spot; Dance of the Hours from La Gioconda
- 1937 season
  - Program No. 1 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1937; wpa_phono_088; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Flag of Victory march; Light Cavalry overture; WPA spot; Irish Tune from County Derry (Londonderry air)(Danny Boy); Shepherd's Hey.
  - Program No. 2 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Madrigal Singers, 1937; wpa_phono_089; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Sing We Enchanted; Mon cœur se recommande a Vous (My heart begs you not to forget me); Au Jolie Bois; In stiller nacht; Petite Nymphe; WPA spot; The Turtle Dove, sung by tenor soloist and chorus; The Springtime of the Year; Revecy Venir du Printans.
  - Program No. 3 Works Progress Administration Presents New York State Symphonic Band, 1937; wpa_phono_090; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to The Magic Flute; WPA spot; Intermezzo from A Dream
  - Program No. 4 Works Progress Administration Presents Juanita Hall Choir, 1937; wpa_phono_091; folk songs and spirituals, by soloists with mixed chorus without accompaniment; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Way over in Beulah Land; The blin' man stood on the road an' cried, arranged by Charles Ford; Walk together Children; WPA spot; Scandalize my Name; Sit down Servant; The ol' ark's a moverin'
  - Program No. 5 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1937; wpa_phono_092; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Marche from Scenes Pittoresques; Overture to The Bohemian Girl; WPA spot; Slavonic Dance no. 1
  - Program No. 6 Works Progress Administration Presents Federal Music Project Chamber Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_093; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to L'isola Disabitata; WPA spot; Overture to The Magic Flute
  - Program No. 7 Works Progress Administration Presents New York State Symphonic Band, 1937; wpa_phono_094; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Dance of the Zingarella; WPA spot; Symphony no. 4, Finale
  - Program No. 8 Works Progress Administration Presents the Madrigal Singers, 1937; wpa_phono_095; mixed chorus without accompanimen; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Clorinda False, Adieu; O vos omnes; Willy, Prithee go to bed; WPA spot; Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John; Die Harmonie in der Eehe; Oh Jesus, Tender Shepherd, Hear.
  - Program No. 9 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1937; wpa_phono_096; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Aires Andaluces; WPA spot; Polish dance No. 1, Op. 3
  - Program No. 10 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Grand Opera Group, 1937; wpa_phono_097; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Fernando del Nonsentsico, selections from Act 1 and 3, sung in English. Potentially the only known recording of the work. This is first broadcasting. Announcer gives synopsis of plot.; WPA spot.
  - Program No. 11 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_098; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    A night in Madrid; WPA spot; Scherzo, At the Fireside, from Symphony No. 1
  - Program No. 12 Works Progress Administration Presents Mexican Orchestra and Chorus, 1937; wpa_phono_099; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture Torre del oro; Me voy para Mexico, rumba (I'm leaving for Mexico City); WPA spot; Hermosas Fuentes, Mexican folk song (Fountain of Love); Jarana Yucateca, Mexican cowboy air.
  - Program No. 13 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_100; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Dream music from Hansel and Gretel; WPA spot; Suite for strings: Sarabande; Gigue; Badinerie
  - Program No. 14 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Colored Chorus, 1937; wpa_phono_101; chorus with piano accompaniment; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Hallelujah chorus from "The Messiah"; O Holy Virgin from "Fra Diavolo"; WPA spot; I Feel a Song Comin' On, uncredited tenor solo; Didn't it Rain from "Noah"; My Lord, What a Morning, Where Shall I Be; John Henry, from production "John Henry".
  - Program No. 15 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Artist Recital, 1937; wpa_phono_102; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Ave Maria, sung by Georgellen Ferguson [?] soprano, Duche Karakiavo [?] violin; Invictus, sung by Charles Henry DuLaplatte [?] basso cantante, uncredited piano accompaniment; WPA spot; Largo al Factotum, from "Barber of Seville", sung by Raphaelle D'Angeles [?] baritone; Vesti la Giubba, from "Pagliacci", sung by Enrico Martinelli tenor, Margaret Reynolds, piano; None but the Lonely Heart, sung by Georgellen Ferguson [?] soprano, Duche Karakiavo [?] violin.
  - Program No. 16 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_103; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Nocturne, from Midsummer Night's Dream; WPA spot; Waltz of the Flower (Valse des fleurs), from The Nutcracker Suite
  - Program No. 17 Works Progress Administration Presents the Los Angeles Concert Band, 1937; wpa_phono_104; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture Baroque, Van Valkenburg [?] composer; Irish Patrol; WPA spot; University of Arizona March
  - Program No. 18 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony, 1937; wpa_phono_105; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Tone poem: Humanitas, part 1 and 2. With comments by the composer via announcer.
  - Program No. 19 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles [A] Capella Choir, 1937; wpa_phono_106; folk songs and spirituals, choral; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Summer is a Coming In (Old English Air), sung in round form, men's & women's choruses; The Lord's Prayer, completely different version of the music, mixed chorus; WPA spot; All through the Night (Welsh Air), men's & women's choruses; Dark Water (Negro Spiritual), mixed chorus.
  - Program No. 20 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony, 1937; wpa_phono_107; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Prelude to Afternoon of a Faun (announced as Afternoon of a Faun); WPA spot; Praeludium
  - Program No. 21 Works Progress Administration Presents Mexican Orchestra and Chorus, 1937; wpa_phono_108; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Marcha Mejico, orchestra, dedicated to the Mexico City Police Band; The Rodeo (El Jaripeo), orchestra with men's & women's choruses, chanting & singing; Ask of the Stars, Beloved (Pregúntale a las estrellas), orchestra with men's & women's choruses; WPA spot; La Marimba, orchestra with men's and women's choruses; La Huasteca, orchestra.
  - Program No. 22 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_109; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Banjo Picker, from Suite of "Piano Pieces"; WPA spot; The Hero, from the Chinese Symphonic suite Prince Su Ming Wang (announcer says Su Wing Wang)
  - Program No. 23 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Colored Chorus, 1937; wpa_phono_110; folk songs and spirituals, solo and choral, with piano accompaniment; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    O, Southland, interpolated with unnamed S. Foster songs, sung by men's & women's chorus with piano accompaniment, uncredited soprano soloist; Great Day, sung by choruses with piano accompaniment; WPA spot; Steal Away, sung by men's & women's chorus, uncredited tenor solo, a capella; Every Time I Feel the Spirit, sung by choruses with piano accompaniment, uncredited female soloist.
  - Program No. 24 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_111; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to the Merry Wives of Windsor; WPA spot; Suite for Strings, 1st movement Sarabande; Suite for Strings, 3rd movement Badinerie
  - Program No. 25 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Folk Lore Choir, 1937; wpa_phono_112; folk songs of various countries, choral and solo, with piano accompaniment; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Italian Peasant Song, sung in Italian; The Virgin of the Angels (La vergine degli angeli) from La Forza del Destino, sung in Italian; Australia (Sea Shanty); WPA spot; Drink to me only withThine eyes (Traditional Air); Why Should I Worry (Russian 'Gypsy' air), sung in Russian; Good Boy (Russian 'Gypsy' air), sung in Russian.
  - Program No. 26 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_113; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Prelude to Tristan and Isolde; WPA spot; Badinerie, from The Suite for Strings
  - Program No. 27 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles [A] Capella Choir, 1937; wpa_phono_114; madrigals and hymns, by men's, women's and mixed choruses; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Sing we enchanted, madrigal; My love dwelt in a northern land; WPA spot; Create in my a pure heart, based on 51st Psalm; Grant unto me the joy of thy salvation, based on 51st Psalm.
  - Program No. 28 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_115; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Le baruffe chiozzotte; WPA spot; Andante cantabile for strings
  - Program No. 29 Works Progress Administration Presents Los Angeles Federal Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_116; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Oberon; WPA spot; Dance of the Reed Flute (Danse des mirlitons), from the Nutcracker suite; Trepak, from the Nutcracker suite
  - Program No. 30 Works Progress Administration Presents Federal Music Project Chamber Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_117; excepts from Gluck's operas; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Don Juan; Air Gai and Lento, from "Iphigenia in Aulis"; Dance of the blessed spirits, from "Orpheus"; Air, from "Iphigenia in Aulis"; Sicilienne, from "Armide"; WPA spot; Air de Ballet, Suite No. 4.
  - Program No. 31 Works Progress Administration Presents New York Federal Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_118; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Prometheus; WPA spot; Invitation to the Dance
  - Program No. 32 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1937; wpa_phono_119; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Dance of the Bayaderes, from "Feramors"; WPA spot; Slavonic Rhapsody
  - Program No. 33 Works Progress Administration Presents Federal Music Project Chamber Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_120; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Symphony in F Minor, La Passione: Adagio; Allegro di Molto, Minuet e Trio; Finale Presto: WPA spot
  - Program No. 34 Works Progress Administration Presents Ensemble Romantique, 1937; wpa_phono_121; string/wind ensemble; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Lydia Savitsaya, harp; Gita Rosova, violin; George Lisitski, flute; and Herman Levine, violoncello. Gavotte; Les tendres reproches; Folk Dance of Brittany (Tambourin); WPA spot; Sarabande; Musette; Dance Minuet.
  - Program No. 35 Works Progress Administration Presents New York Federal Symphony Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_122; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Le Cid; WPA spot on live WPA music concerts; Andante Cantabile, from String quartet in D
  - Program No. 36 Works Progress Administration Presents Federal Music Project Chamber Orchestra, 1937; wpa_phono_123; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Coriolanus, Op. 62; WPA spot; The Last Spring
  - Program No. 37 Works Progress Administration Presents Forum String Quartet of Boston, 1937; wpa_phono_124; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Contrapunctus no. 11, from The Art of the Fugue; WPA spot; First movement: Allegro spiritoso, from Quartet in F major
  - Program No. 38 Works Progress Administration Presents State Symphony of Boston, 1937; wpa_phono_125; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Choral Prelude: Jesu Meine Freude, arranged for strings by Weston L. Brannon [?]; WPA spot; Toccata and Fugue in D Minor, arranged for orchestra by Joseph Zita [?]
  - Program No. 39 Works Progress Administration Presents Modern Rhythm Ensemble of Boston, 1937; wpa_phono_126; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Selections from The Red Mill; WPA spot; Unter dem Lindenbaum, waltz for orchestra; I love Life; art song. Performed by orchestra, men's & women's choruses, and soloists.
  - Program No. 40 Works Progress Administration Presents Commonwealth Symphony and State Chorus [of Boston], 1937; wpa_phono_127; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from The Eighth Beatitude sung in English: "Blessed are those that are persecuted"; WPA spot at midpoint; performed by orchestra, chorus, mezzo-soprano soloist, baritone soloist.
  - Program No. 41 Works Progress Administration Presents Forum String Quartet of Boston, 1937; wpa_phono_128; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Romanze (poco adagio) from Strung Quartet in C minor, Op. 51; WPA spot; Finale from Strung Quartet in C minor, Op. 51
  - Program No. 42 Works Progress Administration Presents State Symphony of Boston, 1937; wpa_phono_129; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Scherzo from Symphony No. 2; WPA spot; A New England Rhapsody (announced as A New Hampshire Rhapsody)
  - Program No. 43 Works Progress Administration Presents Modern Rhythm Ensemble of Boston, 1937; wpa_phono_130; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Marie, female soloist with orchestra; My Moonlight Madonna, orchestra, female soloist, mixed chorus; WPA spot; Fugue and variations in modern rhythm, orchestra; Hallelujah, from "Hit the Deck", orchestra, female soloist, men's and women's choruses, cornet solos.
  - Program No. 44 Works Progress Administration Presents Women's Symphony of Boston, 1937; wpa_phono_131; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Heart wounds; WPA spot; Henry the Eighth: Morris Dance, Shepherd's Dance, Torch Dance
- 1938 season
  - Program No. 45 Works Progress Administration Presents American Folk Singers of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_132; folk songs and spirituals (listed on disc as "Negro spirituals"); Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    King Jesus is a-listening, mixed chorus a capella; That Great gettin' up morning, male soloist with mixed chorus a capella; WPA spot; Chillun, come on home, mixed chorus a capella; Go down, Moses, men's & women's choruses a capella.
  - Program No. 46 Works Progress Administration Presents Commonwealth Symphony and State Chorus of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_133; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Excerpts from Carmen. Concert recital format: orchestra, chorus, and soloists. Cigarette Girls Chorus; WPA spot; Factory Chorus; Gypsy song.
  - Program No. 47 Works Progress Administration Presents Modern Rhythm Ensemble of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_134; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Orchestra, men's chorus, women's chorus, soloists. Why Do I Love You?, from Showboat; St. Louis Blues; WPA spot; Me, Myself, and I; Twilight in Turkey.
  - Program No. 48 Works Progress Administration Presents State Symphony of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_135; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Carnival overture; WPA spot; Ronde d'amour
  - Program No. 49 Works Progress Administration Presents Modern Rhythm Ensemble of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_136; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Time on my hands, concert arrangement by Bert Koulter [?]; Auf Wiedersehn, from The Blue Paradise, orchestra, male & female soloists, chorus; WPA spot; Stardust on the moon, orchestra, chorus, female soloist; Singing a Song to the Stars, orchestra, chorus, female soloist.
  - Program No. 50 Works Progress Administration Presents Forum String Quartet of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_137; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    String Quartet, Op. 44, No. 1: Andante Espressivo Ma Con Moto, 3rd movement; WPA spot; String Quartet, Op. 44, No. 1: Molto Allegro Vivace, 1st movement.
  - Program No. 51 Works Progress Administration Presents Commonwealth Symphony and State Chorus of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_138; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00 (Oversize 1)
    Excerpts from Mendelssohn's Hymn of Praise: The Night is Departing; Let All Men Praise the Lord; WPA spot; Ye Nations Offer to the Lord, orchestra, men's & women's choruses, soloists.
  - Program No. 52 Works Progress Administration Presents State Symphony of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_139; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    The Frogs of Aristophanes, comedy overture, first American broadcast; WPA spot; March of the Little Lead Soldiers
  - Program No. 53 Works Progress Administration Presents Forum String Quartet of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_140; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Lento, from String quartet, Op. 96; WPA spot; Allegretto, from Creole quartet
  - Program No. 54 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1938; wpa_phono_141; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Entrance and March of the Peers, from Iolanthe; The Whisperings of the Flowers; WPA spot; Concerto for Euphonium
  - Program No. 55 Works Progress Administration Presents Commonwealth Symphony and State Chorus of Boston, 1938; wpa_phono_142; selections from Haydn's The Creation; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Performed by orchestra with 65 instruments, 125-voice chorus, soloists. In the Beginning God Created, recitative, baritone with orchestra and men's & women's choruses, tenor; Now Vanish Before the Holy Beams; WPA spot; On The Each Living Soul Awaits; Achieved is the Glorious Work.
  - Program No. 56 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1938; wpa_phono_143; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00
    Overture to Alfieri's 'Saul'; WPA spot; Spring Time, waltz intermezzo
  - Program No. 57 Works Progress Administration Presents [the] Manhattan Concert Band, 1938; wpa_phono_144; Grooved analog disc; running time 15:00